Anna Barn

123 High Street, CoLumbus, OH 12345 annaberg@gmail.com (123)-456-7890

Artist specializing in visual communication with over ten years'experience in professional practice and facilitating learning. Ability to creatively communicate ideas through sculpture, computer-aided design, and mixed media with a basic knowledge of photography. An active artist who regularly exhibits across the U.S. with a work portfolio that can be viewed upon request. Possesses passion and expertise in teaching with the ability to motivate and encourage others.

Education

Master of Fine Arts in Visual Art, Department of Visual Art

University of Kansas. Lawrence, KS September 2007- May 2011

Key Skills

- Strong verbal and communications skills
- Creative
- Organizational and Lesson planning
- Computer-aided design work
- Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator
- Motivating and encouraging others

Certifications

◆ Certified Professional Photographer (CPP) 2009

Professional Experience

Art Director and Educational Manager

Kansas Art Center, Lawrence, KS | May 2017 - Present

- Assume overall responsibility for the art center's educational programs
- Plan and deliver community classes for kids and adults
- Design and hang artwork
- Exhibit mixed media art installations at the art center

Art Assistant

Kansas Art Center, Lawrence, KS I Jan 2008 - May 2017

- Assisted in the delivery of art classes
- Worked with groups and individual students
- Prepared art materials

Exhibitions throughout the U.S.

May 2012 - Present

- Exhibit work at galleries and art exhibitions throughout the U.S.
- Take part in group and solo shows